{
	"description": "アーヴ語",
	"deck": [
		{ "question": "<ゴースロス>の戦い", "answers": [ "スラーショス・ゴースロト" ]},
		{ "question": "〜・環", "answers": [ "スペーシュ・〜" ]},
		{ "question": "〜室", "answers": [ "シル・〜" ]},
		{ "question": "〜科", "answers": [ "ファズィア・〜" ]},
		{ "question": "〜長", "answers": [ "ワス・〜" ]},
		{ "question": "ご主君", "answers": [ "ファル・ローニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "ささやかな戦い", "answers": [ "スラーショス・スワーファ" ]},
		{ "question": "つなぎ", "answers": [ "ソルフ" ]},
		{ "question": "ばか", "answers": [ "オーニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "わが主", "answers": [ "ファル・ローニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "わが主君", "answers": [ "ファル・スィーフ" ]},
		{ "question": "わが君", "answers": [ "ファル・ローニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "わが娘", "answers": [ "ファル・フリューム" ]},
		{ "question": "わが愛", "answers": [ "ファル・ネージュ" ]},
		{ "question": "わたしの可愛い殿下", "answers": [ "ファル・フィア・クフェーナ" ]},
		{ "question": "アファレーシュ伯国", "answers": [ "ドリュヒューニュ・アファーレク" ]},
		{ "question": "アブリアルの耳", "answers": [ "ヌイ・アブリアルサル" ]},
		{ "question": "アブリアルの華", "answers": [ "グナー・アブリアルサル" ]},
		{ "question": "アブリアル伯国", "answers": [ "ドリュヒューニュ・アブリアルサル" ]},
		{ "question": "アブリアル伯爵", "answers": [ "ドリュー・アブリアルサル" ]},
		{ "question": "アプティック伯国", "answers": [ "ドリュヒューニュ・アプティカル" ]},
		{ "question": "アプティック星系", "answers": [ "キーヨース・アプティカル" ]},
		{ "question": "アプティック門沖会戦", "answers": [ "ライシャカル・ウェク・ソーダル・アプティカル" ]},
		{ "question": "アプティック防衛艦隊", "answers": [ "レクポリア・アプティカル" ]},
		{ "question": "アプティック防衛艦隊旗艦", "answers": [ "グラーガ・レクポレール・アプティカル" ]},
		{ "question": "アーヴ(の)〜", "answers": [ "バール・〜" ]},
		{ "question": "アーヴによる人類帝国", "answers": [ "フリューバル・グレール・ゴル・バーリ" ]},
		{ "question": "アーヴの名誉", "answers": [ "バール・レペーヌ" ]},
		{ "question": "アーヴの微笑", "answers": [ "バール・エヴォス" ]},
		{ "question": "アーヴの歴史", "answers": [ "バール・グレール" ]},
		{ "question": "アーヴの流儀", "answers": [ "バール・ゲルサス" ]},
		{ "question": "アーヴの腕", "answers": [ "バール・セーダ" ]},
		{ "question": "アーヴの誇り", "answers": [ "バール・レペーヌ" ]},
		{ "question": "アーヴの都", "answers": [ "バール・ロニート" ]},
		{ "question": "アーヴ史", "answers": [ "バール・グレール" ]},
		{ "question": "アーヴ帝国", "answers": [ "バール・フリューバル" ]},
		{ "question": "アーヴ猫", "answers": [ "デューク" ]},
		{ "question": "アーヴ貴族", "answers": [ "バール・スィーフ" ]},
		{ "question": "イリーシュ王国", "answers": [ "フェーク・イリク" ]},
		{ "question": "イリーシュ王家", "answers": [ "ラルティエ・イリク" ]},
		{ "question": "イリーシュ門", "answers": [ "ソード・イリク" ]},
		{ "question": "ウィンブル門", "answers": [ "ソード・ウィンブル" ]},
		{ "question": "ウェスコー王国", "answers": [ "フェーク・ウェスコール" ]},
		{ "question": "ウェスコー王家", "answers": [ "ラルティエ・ウェスコール" ]},
		{ "question": "ウェスコー門", "answers": [ "ソード・ウェスコール" ]},
		{ "question": "ウェムダイス子爵", "answers": [ "ベール・ウェムダイサル" ]},
		{ "question": "ウェーレ公国", "answers": [ "レクリューニュ・ウェーレル" ]},
		{ "question": "エストート公国", "answers": [ "レクリューニュ・エスタートル" ]},
		{ "question": "ガムテーシュ子爵領", "answers": [ "ベールスコル・ガムテク" ]},
		{ "question": "ガムヴ公爵公子", "answers": [ "ヤルルーク・レークル・ガムブ" ]},
		{ "question": "クリューヴ王", "answers": [ "ラルス・クリュブ" ]},
		{ "question": "クリューヴ王宮", "answers": [ "ラルベイ・クリュブ" ]},
		{ "question": "クリューヴ王家", "answers": [ "ラルティエ・クリュブ" ]},
		{ "question": "クリューヴ王殿下", "answers": [ "フィア・ラルト・クリュブ" ]},
		{ "question": "クリューヴ門", "answers": [ "ソード・クリュブ" ]},
		{ "question": "クローハ二二九門", "answers": [ "ソード・マトマトソクンナ・クローハル" ]},
		{ "question": "ケイシュ一九三門", "answers": [ "ソード・キュトソクンビナ・ケイク" ]},
		{ "question": "ゲムファーズ伯爵", "answers": [ "ドリュー・ゲムファド" ]},
		{ "question": "ゴガーフ伯国", "answers": [ "ドリュヒューニュ・ゴガム" ]},
		{ "question": "ゴクローシュ建艦厰", "answers": [ "ロール・ゴクロク" ]},
		{ "question": "ジントの怒り", "answers": [ "セーロス・ジンタル" ]},
		{ "question": "スィトゥール捕虜収容所", "answers": [ "ロニューグヴィ・スィトゥル" ]},
		{ "question": "スィーヴ八八二門", "answers": [ "ソード・ガガマタ・スイブ" ]},
		{ "question": "スカレーシュ門沖会戦", "answers": [ "ライシャカル・ウェク・ソーダル・スカレク" ]},
		{ "question": "スキール王家", "answers": [ "ラルティエ・スキル" ]},
		{ "question": "スファグノーフ伯国", "answers": [ "ドリュヒューニュ・スファグノム" ]},
		{ "question": "スファグノーフ侯国", "answers": [ "レーバヒューニュ・スファグノム" ]},
		{ "question": "スファグノーフ侯国警固隊", "answers": [ "レートフェクラシュ・スファグノム" ]},
		{ "question": "スファグノーフ侯爵", "answers": [ "レーブ・スファグノム" ]},
		{ "question": "スファグノーフ侯爵家", "answers": [ "レーブジェ・スファグノム" ]},
		{ "question": "スファグノーフ侯爵閣下", "answers": [ "ローニュ・レーバル・スファグノム" ]},
		{ "question": "スファグノーフ基地", "answers": [ "ロニード・スファグノム" ]},
		{ "question": "スファグノーフ子爵", "answers": [ "ベール・スファグノム" ]},
		{ "question": "スファグノーフ子爵家", "answers": [ "ベーリェ・スファグノム" ]},
		{ "question": "スファグノーフ子爵領", "answers": [ "ベールスコル・スファグノム" ]},
		{ "question": "スファグノーフ門", "answers": [ "ソード・スファグノム" ]},
		{ "question": "スファグノーフ門沖会戦", "answers": [ "ライシャカル・ウェク・ソーダル・スファグノム" ]},
		{ "question": "スポールの紅瞳", "answers": [ "キレーフ・ピアナ・スポル" ]},
		{ "question": "スュルグゼーデ王国", "answers": [ "フェーク・スュルグゼーデル" ]},
		{ "question": "スュルグゼーデ王家", "answers": [ "ラルティエ・スュルグゼーデル" ]},
		{ "question": "スュール建艦厰", "answers": [ "ロール・スューラル" ]},
		{ "question": "セズレーニュ男爵", "answers": [ "リューフ・セズレン" ]},
		{ "question": "ダルマプ門", "answers": [ "ソード・ダルマパル" ]},
		{ "question": "ティセーヌ伯国", "answers": [ "ドリュヒューニュ・ティセーナル" ]},
		{ "question": "ティセーヌ伯爵", "answers": [ "ドリュー・ティセーナル" ]},
		{ "question": "ティセーヌ伯爵閣下", "answers": [ "ローニュ・ドリュール・ティセーナル" ]},
		{ "question": "デメテル門", "answers": [ "ソード・デメテル" ]},
		{ "question": "デルクトゥー宇宙港", "answers": [ "ビドート・デルクトゥール" ]},
		{ "question": "トライフ艦隊", "answers": [ "ビュール・トライム" ]},
		{ "question": "トライフ艦隊旗艦", "answers": [ "グラーガ・ビューラル・トライム" ]},
		{ "question": "ドゥガス猊下", "answers": [ "ニソス・ドゥガス" ]},
		{ "question": "ドゥサーニュ殿下", "answers": [ "フィア・ドゥサン" ]},
		{ "question": "ドゥスーム猊下", "answers": [ "ニソス・ドゥスーマル" ]},
		{ "question": "ドゥセーフ猊下", "answers": [ "ニソス・ドゥセム" ]},
		{ "question": "ドゥネー星界軍大学", "answers": [ "ヴォスクラ・ドゥネール" ]},
		{ "question": "ドゥヒール殿下", "answers": [ "フィア・ドゥヒル" ]},
		{ "question": "ドゥビュース殿下", "answers": [ "フィア・ドゥビュト","フィア・ドゥビューサル" ]},
		{ "question": "ドゥラーズ猊下", "answers": [ "ニソス・ドゥラド" ]},
		{ "question": "ハイド伯国", "answers": [ "ドリュヒューニュ・ハイダル" ]},
		{ "question": "ハイド伯爵", "answers": [ "ドリュー・ハイダル" ]},
		{ "question": "ハイド伯爵公子", "answers": [ "ヤルルーク・ドリュール・ハイダル" ]},
		{ "question": "ハイド伯爵公子閣下", "answers": [ "ローニュ・ヤルルーカル・ドリュール・ハイダル" ]},
		{ "question": "ハイド伯爵城館", "answers": [ "ガリーシュ・ドリュール・ハイダル" ]},
		{ "question": "ハイド伯爵家", "answers": [ "ドリュージェ・ハイダル" ]},
		{ "question": "ハイド伯爵閣下", "answers": [ "ローニュ・ドリュール・ハイダル" ]},
		{ "question": "バルグゼーデ王家", "answers": [ "ラルティエ・バルグゼーデル" ]},
		{ "question": "バルケー王", "answers": [ "ラルス・バルケール" ]},
		{ "question": "バルケー王家", "answers": [ "ラルティエ・バルケール" ]},
		{ "question": "バルケー王殿下", "answers": [ "フィア・ラルト・バルケール" ]},
		{ "question": "パリューニュ子爵", "answers": [ "ベール・パリュン" ]},
		{ "question": "パリューニュ子爵城館", "answers": [ "ガリューシュ・ベル・パリュン" ]},
		{ "question": "パリューニュ子爵殿下", "answers": [ "フィア・ベル・パリュン" ]},
		{ "question": "パリューニュ子爵領", "answers": [ "ベールスコル・パリュン" ]},
		{ "question": "ビスケース伯国", "answers": [ "ドリュヒューニュ・ビスケーサル" ]},
		{ "question": "ビスレ伯国", "answers": [ "ドリュヒューニュ・ビスレル" ]},
		{ "question": "フェブダーシュの淑女", "answers": [ "ロージュ・フェブダク" ]},
		{ "question": "フェブダーシュ前男爵閣下", "answers": [ "ローニュ・リュム・レカ・フェブダク" ]},
		{ "question": "フェブダーシュ男爵家", "answers": [ "リュミェ・フェブダク" ]},
		{ "question": "フェブダーシュ男爵帝都城館", "answers": [ "ガリーシュ・アロク・リュム・フェブダク" ]},
		{ "question": "フェブダーシュ男爵領", "answers": [ "リュームスコル・フェブダク" ]},
		{ "question": "フェブダーシュ男爵領暦", "answers": [ "フェブダーショス" ]},
		{ "question": "フェブダーシュ男爵領管制", "answers": [ "ブリューセ・リュームスコル・フェブダク" ]},
		{ "question": "フェブダーシュ男爵館", "answers": [ "リューメクス・フェブダク" ]},
		{ "question": "フェブダーシュ男爵館家政室", "answers": [ "バンゾール・ガリク・リューメクト・フェブダク" ]},
		{ "question": "フェブダーシュ門", "answers": [ "ソード・フェブダク" ]},
		{ "question": "フリーザ伯国", "answers": [ "ドリュヒューニュ・フリーザル" ]},
		{ "question": "ブェブダーシュ男爵", "answers": [ "リューフ・フェブダク" ]},
		{ "question": "プラキアの想い出", "answers": [ "ワベード・プラケール" ]},
		{ "question": "プラキア卿", "answers": [ "キュア・プラケール" ]},
		{ "question": "プラズマ", "answers": [ "グノー" ]},
		{ "question": "ベートゥール建艦厰", "answers": [ "ロール・ベートゥル" ]},
		{ "question": "ミスケル門", "answers": [ "ソード・ミスケラル" ]},
		{ "question": "ミスケル防衛艦隊", "answers": [ "レクポリア・ミスケラル" ]},
		{ "question": "ユーニュ三〇三星系", "answers": [ "キーヨース・ビボルビナ・ユン" ]},
		{ "question": "ヨニー伯国", "answers": [ "ドリュヒューニュ・ヨニール" ]},
		{ "question": "ラクテーシュ侯国", "answers": [ "ドリュヒューニュ・ラクリュク" ]},
		{ "question": "ラスィース王国", "answers": [ "フェーク・ラスィーサル" ]},
		{ "question": "ラスィース王家", "answers": [ "ラルティエ・ラスィーサル" ]},
		{ "question": "ラフィールの変身", "answers": [ "ゴローコス・ラフィル" ]},
		{ "question": "ラフィール殿下", "answers": [ "フィア・ラフィル" ]},
		{ "question": "ラムリューヌ殿下", "answers": [ "フィア・ラムリューナル" ]},
		{ "question": "ラムローニュ猊下", "answers": [ "ニソス・ラムロン" ]},
		{ "question": "ラメーム猊下", "answers": [ "ニソス・ラメーマル" ]},
		{ "question": "ラモーズ猊下", "answers": [ "ニソス・ラムロード" ]},
		{ "question": "ラルブリューヴ鎮守府", "answers": [ "シュテューム・ラルブリュブ" ]},
		{ "question": "リネー伯国", "answers": [ "ドリュヒューニュ・リネール" ]},
		{ "question": "ルーヌ・ビーガ市", "answers": [ "バーシュ・ルーナル・ビーガ" ]},
		{ "question": "レスポー建艦厰", "answers": [ "ロール・レスポール" ]},
		{ "question": "レトパーニュ大公国", "answers": [ "ニーフューニュ・レトパン" ]},
		{ "question": "レトパーニュ大公爵", "answers": [ "ニーフ・レトパン" ]},
		{ "question": "レトパーニュ大公爵公女", "answers": [ "ヤルリューム・ニム・レトパン" ]},
		{ "question": "レトパーニュ大公爵城館", "answers": [ "ガリーシュ・ニム・レトパン" ]},
		{ "question": "レトパーニュ大公爵家", "answers": [ "ニーミェ・レトパン" ]},
		{ "question": "レトパーニュ門", "answers": [ "ソード・レトパン" ]},
		{ "question": "ヴォベイルネー工厰", "answers": [ "ロール・ヴォベイルネール" ]},
		{ "question": "ヴォベイルネー鎮守府", "answers": [ "シュテューム・ヴォベイルネール" ]},
		{ "question": "ヴォベイルネー門", "answers": [ "ソード・ヴォベイルネール" ]},
		{ "question": "ヴォービノート建艦厰", "answers": [ "ロール・ヴォービノータル" ]},
		{ "question": "ヴォーラーシュ伯国", "answers": [ "ドリュヒューニュ・ヴォーラク" ]},
		{ "question": "ヴォーラーシュ伯国管制", "answers": [ "ブリューセ・ドリューヒュン・ヴォーラク" ]},
		{ "question": "ヴォーラーシュ伯爵家", "answers": [ "ドリュージェ・ヴォーラク" ]},
		{ "question": "ヴォーラーシュ門", "answers": [ "ソード・ヴォーラク" ]},
		{ "question": "一等勲爵士", "answers": [ "ラローシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "一般電波紋鍵", "answers": [ "セージュ・デファト・ヘータ" ]},
		{ "question": "上皇", "answers": [ "ファニーガ" ]},
		{ "question": "上皇会議", "answers": [ "ルゼー・ファニガラク" ]},
		{ "question": "下げ飾り", "answers": [ "フラーフ" ]},
		{ "question": "与圧兜", "answers": [ "サプート" ]},
		{ "question": "与圧服", "answers": [ "ゴネー" ]},
		{ "question": "中心領域", "answers": [ "ソール・バンダク" ]},
		{ "question": "主 計百翔長", "answers": [ "ボモワス・サゾイル" ]},
		{ "question": "主任(家士)", "answers": [ "アルム・〜" ]},
		{ "question": "主思考結晶", "answers": [ "オブダテューキル" ]},
		{ "question": "主機関", "answers": [ "オプセー" ]},
		{ "question": "主計修技館", "answers": [ "ケンルー・サゾイル" ]},
		{ "question": "主計修技館生活諸規則", "answers": [ "リウェール・クナソト・ケンルール・サゾイル" ]},
		{ "question": "主計元帥", "answers": [ "スペーヌ・サゾイル" ]},
		{ "question": "主計准提督", "answers": [ "ロイフローデ・サゾイル" ]},
		{ "question": "主計列翼翔士", "answers": [ "フェクトダイ・サゾイル" ]},
		{ "question": "主計前衛翔士", "answers": [ "レクレー・サゾイル" ]},
		{ "question": "主計副百翔長", "answers": [ "ロイボモワス・サゾイル" ]},
		{ "question": "主計十翔長", "answers": [ "ローワス・サゾイル" ]},
		{ "question": "主計千翔長", "answers": [ "シュワス・サゾイル" ]},
		{ "question": "主計大提督", "answers": [ "フォフローデ・サゾイル" ]},
		{ "question": "主計後衛翔士", "answers": [ "リニェール・サゾイル" ]},
		{ "question": "主計提督", "answers": [ "フローデ・サゾイル" ]},
		{ "question": "主計科", "answers": [ "サーゾイ","サゾイル" ]},
		{ "question": "主計翔士", "answers": [ "ロダイル・サゾイル" ]},
		{ "question": "乗員", "answers": [ "ソーク" ]},
		{ "question": "乗用艇", "answers": [ "ワーフ" ]},
		{ "question": "乾燥機", "answers": [ "ビムーキア" ]},
		{ "question": "予備役翔士", "answers": [ "ロダイル・キサイナ" ]},
		{ "question": "二等勲爵士", "answers": [ "キゼー" ]},
		{ "question": "交通艇", "answers": [ "ポーニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "人工子宮", "answers": [ "ヤーニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "人類", "answers": [ "グレー" ]},
		{ "question": "代官", "answers": [ "トセール" ]},
		{ "question": "任務", "answers": [ "スコイコス" ]},
		{ "question": "任務番号", "answers": [ "フタリア・スロフォト" ]},
		{ "question": "会社", "answers": [ "ガリュール" ]},
		{ "question": "伯国", "answers": [ "ドリュヒューニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "伯爵", "answers": [ "ドリュー" ]},
		{ "question": "伯爵位", "answers": [ "ドリューラジュ" ]},
		{ "question": "伯爵公子", "answers": [ "ヤルルーク・ドリュール" ]},
		{ "question": "伯爵公子閣下", "answers": [ "ローニュ・ヤルルーカル・ドリュール" ]},
		{ "question": "伯爵家", "answers": [ "ドリュージェ" ]},
		{ "question": "伯爵閣下", "answers": [ "ローニュ・ドリュール" ]},
		{ "question": "似我蜂", "answers": [ "ロイル" ]},
		{ "question": "位階", "answers": [ "レーニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "作戦参謀", "answers": [ "カーサリア・ヨクスクロト" ]},
		{ "question": "作戦室", "answers": [ "シル・ヨクスクロト" ]},
		{ "question": "使節庁", "answers": [ "ゲーク・スコファリメール" ]},
		{ "question": "侍従", "answers": [ "ベイケブリア" ]},
		{ "question": "侍従長", "answers": [ "ワス・ベイケブレール" ]},
		{ "question": "侯国", "answers": [ "レーバヒューニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "侯爵", "answers": [ "レーブ" ]},
		{ "question": "侯爵家", "answers": [ "レーブジェ" ]},
		{ "question": "信号", "answers": [ "アーガ" ]},
		{ "question": "修技生", "answers": [ "ベネー" ]},
		{ "question": "修技館", "answers": [ "ケンルー" ]},
		{ "question": "個隊", "answers": [ "スューフ" ]},
		{ "question": "停止状態", "answers": [ "スコールタフ" ]},
		{ "question": "停滞状態", "answers": [ "スコールタフ" ]},
		{ "question": "偵察分艦隊", "answers": [ "ヤドビュール・ウセム" ]},
		{ "question": "偵察戦隊", "answers": [ "ソーヴ・ウセム" ]},
		{ "question": "偵察艇", "answers": [ "ボデーミア" ]},
		{ "question": "儀仗従士", "answers": [ "サーシュ・イダル" ]},
		{ "question": "元帥", "answers": [ "スペーヌ" ]},
		{ "question": "先任〜", "answers": [ "アルム・〜" ]},
		{ "question": "先任参謀", "answers": [ "アルム・カーサリア" ]},
		{ "question": "先任砲術士", "answers": [ "アルム・トラーキア" ]},
		{ "question": "先任翔士", "answers": [ "アルム・ロダイル" ]},
		{ "question": "先任航法士", "answers": [ "アルム・リルビガ" ]},
		{ "question": "先任通信士", "answers": [ "アルム・ドロキア" ]},
		{ "question": "光子科", "answers": [ "ファズィア・ダテュークリール" ]},
		{ "question": "光源弾倉", "answers": [ "ヤペール" ]},
		{ "question": "八つの頚をもつ竜", "answers": [ "ガフトノーシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "八王国", "answers": [ "ガ・フェーク" ]},
		{ "question": "八王家", "answers": [ "ガ・ラルティエ" ]},
		{ "question": "八門の都", "answers": [ "ビロート・ガソーダル" ]},
		{ "question": "八頸竜", "answers": [ "ガフトノーシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "公国", "answers": [ "レクリューニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "公女", "answers": [ "ヤルリューム" ]},
		{ "question": "公女閣下", "answers": [ "ローニュ・ヤルリューマル" ]},
		{ "question": "公子", "answers": [ "ヤルルーク" ]},
		{ "question": "公爵", "answers": [ "レークル" ]},
		{ "question": "兵員輸送", "answers": [ "レーヴァス" ]},
		{ "question": "兵籍番号", "answers": [ "フタリア・ボスナル" ]},
		{ "question": "円匙", "answers": [ "クフォー" ]},
		{ "question": "円扉", "answers": [ "ボード" ]},
		{ "question": "准提督", "answers": [ "ロイフローデ" ]},
		{ "question": "准提督閣下", "answers": [ "ローニュ・ロイフローデル" ]},
		{ "question": "凝集光", "answers": [ "クランラジュ" ]},
		{ "question": "凝集光砲", "answers": [ "ヴォークラーニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "凝集光銃", "answers": [ "クラーニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "分艦隊", "answers": [ "ヤドビュール" ]},
		{ "question": "分艦隊司令官", "answers": [ "レシェーク・ヤドビューラル" ]},
		{ "question": "分艦隊司令部", "answers": [ "グラーガーフ・ヤドビューラル " ]},
		{ "question": "分艦隊紋章旗", "answers": [ "グラー・ヤドビューラル" ]},
		{ "question": "列翼翔士", "answers": [ "フェクトダイ" ]},
		{ "question": "初陣", "answers": [ "フィートラショス" ]},
		{ "question": "判定委員", "answers": [ "ラベスィア" ]},
		{ "question": "制御卓", "answers": [ "クロウ" ]},
		{ "question": "制御篭手", "answers": [ "グーヘーク" ]},
		{ "question": "制御表層", "answers": [ "ファロール・ソク" ]},
		{ "question": "前バルケー王", "answers": [ "ラルス・レカ・バルケール" ]},
		{ "question": "前フェブダーシュ男爵", "answers": [ "リューフ・レカ・フェブダク" ]},
		{ "question": "前男爵", "answers": [ "リューフ・レカ" ]},
		{ "question": "前男爵閣下", "answers": [ "ローニュ・リュム・レカ" ]},
		{ "question": "前皇帝", "answers": [ "スピュネージュ・レカ" ]},
		{ "question": "前衛翔士", "answers": [ "レクレー" ]},
		{ "question": "副代表", "answers": [ "ロイルサーガ" ]},
		{ "question": "副司令長官", "answers": [ "ロイグラハレル" ]},
		{ "question": "副官", "answers": [ "ルーキア" ]},
		{ "question": "副百翔長", "answers": [ "ロイボモワス" ]},
		{ "question": "副長", "answers": [ "ルーセ" ]},
		{ "question": "副長官", "answers": [ "ロイグラハレル" ]},
		{ "question": "加速", "answers": [ "カイムホス" ]},
		{ "question": "勅任翔士", "answers": [ "セドラリア" ]},
		{ "question": "勝利の舞い", "answers": [ "ワドロス・サーソト" ]},
		{ "question": "勝利を", "answers": [ "サーソート" ]},
		{ "question": "募集事務所", "answers": [ "バンゾール・ルドロト" ]},
		{ "question": "医療支援機", "answers": [ "クリュールポーク" ]},
		{ "question": "十翔長", "answers": [ "ローワス" ]},
		{ "question": "千翔長", "answers": [ "シュワス" ]},
		{ "question": "協力要請", "answers": [ "ラドーフォス・ロフォト" ]},
		{ "question": "参謀", "answers": [ "カーサリア" ]},
		{ "question": "参謀徽章", "answers": [ "クラペーフ" ]},
		{ "question": "参謀長", "answers": [ "ワス・カーサレール" ]},
		{ "question": "双翼の頭環", "answers": [ "アルファ・マブラル" ]},
		{ "question": "双翼頭環", "answers": [ "アルファ・マブラル" ]},
		{ "question": "反物質工場", "answers": [ "ヨーズ" ]},
		{ "question": "反物質燃料", "answers": [ "ベーシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "反物質燃料工場", "answers": [ "ヨーズ" ]},
		{ "question": "反物質燃料槽小惑星", "answers": [ "ソブ・ベケーカル" ]},
		{ "question": "反物質燃料槽検査船", "answers": [ "ラデウィア・ベケーカル" ]},
		{ "question": "反物質燃料製造工場", "answers": [ "ヨーズ" ]},
		{ "question": "反陽子砲", "answers": [ "ルニュージュ" ]},
		{ "question": "号笛", "answers": [ "メー" ]},
		{ "question": "司令", "answers": [ "サレール" ]},
		{ "question": "司令官", "answers": [ "レシェーク" ]},
		{ "question": "司令官室", "answers": [ "シル・レシェーカル" ]},
		{ "question": "司令座", "answers": [ "グラハレリバーシュ","レシェーキバーシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "司令座艦橋", "answers": [ "ガホール・グラール" ]},
		{ "question": "司令部", "answers": [ "グラーガーフ" ]},
		{ "question": "司令部要員", "answers": [ "カボース" ]},
		{ "question": "司令長官", "answers": [ "グラハレル" ]},
		{ "question": "司令長官殿下", "answers": [ "フィア・グラハレル" ]},
		{ "question": "司厨従士", "answers": [ "サーシュ・クネイル" ]},
		{ "question": "合成樹脂", "answers": [ "ゲーニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "同胞", "answers": [ "カルサール" ]},
		{ "question": "商店館", "answers": [ "イレーヴ" ]},
		{ "question": "商船団", "answers": [ "カソベールラシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "商館", "answers": [ "ゲーク" ]},
		{ "question": "商館長", "answers": [ "ワス・ゲカル" ]},
		{ "question": "嚮導突撃艦", "answers": [ "アルム・ゲール" ]},
		{ "question": "四カ国連合", "answers": [ "ブルーヴォス・ゴス・スュン" ]},
		{ "question": "四等従士", "answers": [ "サーシュ・ゴーナ" ]},
		{ "question": "国民", "answers": [ "レーフ" ]},
		{ "question": "国章", "answers": [ "ニグラー" ]},
		{ "question": "地上世界", "answers": [ "ナヘーヌ" ]},
		{ "question": "地上世界出身者", "answers": [ "ナヘヌード" ]},
		{ "question": "地上人", "answers": [ "アイブ" ]},
		{ "question": "地上戦", "answers": [ "ナヘーヌヨクス" ]},
		{ "question": "地上車", "answers": [ "フレリア" ]},
		{ "question": "城館", "answers": [ "ガリーシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "埠頭", "answers": [ "ベス" ]},
		{ "question": "執務室", "answers": [ "ガホール" ]},
		{ "question": "培養牧場", "answers": [ "バセーヴ" ]},
		{ "question": "基地", "answers": [ "ロニード" ]},
		{ "question": "士族", "answers": [ "リューク" ]},
		{ "question": "士族さま", "answers": [ "キューク・リューカル" ]},
		{ "question": "士族身分", "answers": [ "リュークラジュ" ]},
		{ "question": "大公国", "answers": [ "ニーフューニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "大公爵", "answers": [ "ローニュ・ニム" ]},
		{ "question": "大公爵公女", "answers": [ "ヤルリューム・ニム" ]},
		{ "question": "大公爵家", "answers": [ "ニーミェ" ]},
		{ "question": "大提督", "answers": [ "フォフローデ" ]},
		{ "question": "大爆誕", "answers": [ "ドリアロン" ]},
		{ "question": "大追跡", "answers": [ "ヴォーウェーコス" ]},
		{ "question": "天川銀河", "answers": [ "エルークファ" ]},
		{ "question": "天川門群", "answers": [ "ソードラシュ・エルークファル" ]},
		{ "question": "天浬", "answers": [ "ケドレル" ]},
		{ "question": "天節", "answers": [ "ディグル" ]},
		{ "question": "天翔る迷惑", "answers": [ "ロビアシュ・セスラ" ]},
		{ "question": "姓称号", "answers": [ "サペーヌ" ]},
		{ "question": "姫さま", "answers": [ "キュアラ" ]},
		{ "question": "姿勢制御機関", "answers": [ "ロイラーガ" ]},
		{ "question": "娘", "answers": [ "フリューム" ]},
		{ "question": "子爵", "answers": [ "ベール" ]},
		{ "question": "子爵家", "answers": [ "ベーリェ" ]},
		{ "question": "子爵殿下", "answers": [ "フィア・ベル" ]},
		{ "question": "子爵領", "answers": [ "ベールスコル" ]},
		{ "question": "子羊", "answers": [ "サゲーシュ・ソクリュズ" ]},
		{ "question": "宇宙", "answers": [ "ケサース" ]},
		{ "question": "宇宙の民", "answers": [ "ケサテュード" ]},
		{ "question": "宇宙港", "answers": [ "ビドート" ]},
		{ "question": "宇宙空間", "answers": [ "ダーズ" ]},
		{ "question": "宇宙艦", "answers": [ "メーニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "完全移動状態", "answers": [ "ノークタフ・バタ" ]},
		{ "question": "客船", "answers": [ "レーヴ" ]},
		{ "question": "宮中序列", "answers": [ "ダルムサス・ヴォフリール" ]},
		{ "question": "宮廷", "answers": [ "フリリーシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "宰相府", "answers": [ "ボーシミアシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "宰相閣下", "answers": [ "ローニュ・ボーシム" ]},
		{ "question": "家宰", "answers": [ "ガポティア" ]},
		{ "question": "家徴", "answers": [ "ワリート" ]},
		{ "question": "家政室", "answers": [ "バンゾール・ガリク" ]},
		{ "question": "家政室主任家士", "answers": [ "アルム・ゴニュード" ]},
		{ "question": "家紋", "answers": [ "アージュ" ]},
		{ "question": "家臣", "answers": [ "ゴスク" ]},
		{ "question": "家臣どの", "answers": [ "ゴスク・ラン" ]},
		{ "question": "家臣団", "answers": [ "ゴスクラシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "家風", "answers": [ "ジェデール" ]},
		{ "question": "寝室係", "answers": [ "ディアファセール" ]},
		{ "question": "対消滅機関", "answers": [ "フリセースィア" ]},
		{ "question": "射撃", "answers": [ "ウールタフ" ]},
		{ "question": "少年", "answers": [ "ファネブ" ]},
		{ "question": "尖筆", "answers": [ "スュージュ" ]},
		{ "question": "巡察艦", "answers": [ "レスィー" ]},
		{ "question": "工作艦", "answers": [ "ダウスィア" ]},
		{ "question": "工厰", "answers": [ "ロール" ]},
		{ "question": "工場", "answers": [ "ヨーズ" ]},
		{ "question": "帝位", "answers": [ "スケムソラジュ" ]},
		{ "question": "帝位継承", "answers": [ "キルグラジュ" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国", "answers": [ "フリューバル" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国には勝利を", "answers": [ "サーソート・フリューバラリ・ア" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国の〜", "answers": [ "ルエ" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国の国民", "answers": [ "ルエ・レーフ" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国の娘", "answers": [ "フリューム・フリューバラル" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国の戦場", "answers": [ "ユクラーヴ・フリューバラル" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国の揺籃", "answers": [ "ギュルソーグ・フリューバラル" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国の法", "answers": [ "ルエ・ラゼ−ム" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国の王女", "answers": [ "ラルトネー・フリューバラル" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国は汝を忘れじ", "answers": [ "フリューバル・ア・ダール・フローネデ" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国代表", "answers": [ "ルエ・ルサーガ" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国伯爵", "answers": [ "ルエ・ドリュー" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国侯爵", "answers": [ "ルエ・レーブ" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国元帥", "answers": [ "ルエ・スペーヌ" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国公爵", "answers": [ "ルエ・レークル" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国副代表", "answers": [ "ルエ・ロイルサーガ" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国創設以前", "answers": [ "バイ・ルエコト" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国商船団", "answers": [ "ルエ・カソベールラシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国国歌", "answers": [ "ルエ・オル" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国国民", "answers": [ "ルエ・レーフ" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国国章", "answers": [ "ルエ・ニグラー" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国基準通貨", "answers": [ "スカール" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国宰相", "answers": [ "ルエ・ボーシフ" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国旗", "answers": [ "ルエ・ニグラー" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国星界軍", "answers": [ "ルエ・ラブール" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国星界軍管理区画", "answers": [ "ボレーヴ・ルエ・ラブーラル" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国暦", "answers": [ "ルエコス" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国歴前", "answers": [ "バイ・ルエコト" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国法", "answers": [ "ルエ・ラゼ−ム" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国男爵", "answers": [ "ルエ・リューフ" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国紋章旗", "answers": [ "ルエ・ニグラー" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国紋章院", "answers": [ "ガール・スカス" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国臣民", "answers": [ "ルエ・ビサール" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国艦隊", "answers": [ "ルエ・ビュール" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国艦隊司令長官", "answers": [ "グラハレル・ルエ・ビューラル" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国艦隊司令長官殿下", "answers": [ "フィア・グラハレル・ルエ・ビューラル" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国貴族", "answers": [ "ルエ・スィーフ" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国貴顕録", "answers": [ "ルエ・ララサ" ]},
		{ "question": "帝国高等法院", "answers": [ "スカス・ラザソト" ]},
		{ "question": "帝室", "answers": [ "ルエジェ" ]},
		{ "question": "帝宮", "answers": [ "ルエベイ" ]},
		{ "question": "帝宮にて", "answers": [ "ルエベイル" ]},
		{ "question": "帝都", "answers": [ "アローシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "帝都交通庁", "answers": [ "スポーデ・ビル・アロク" ]},
		{ "question": "帝都城館", "answers": [ "ガリーシュ・アロク" ]},
		{ "question": "帯留", "answers": [ "アペズ" ]},
		{ "question": "幕僚", "answers": [ "スペルーシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "平面宇宙", "answers": [ "ファーズ" ]},
		{ "question": "平面宇宙図", "answers": [ "ヤ・ファド" ]},
		{ "question": "平面宇宙技術", "answers": [ "ファズ・ファーゾト" ]},
		{ "question": "平面宇宙航法", "answers": [ "ファーゾス" ]},
		{ "question": "平面宇宙航法理論", "answers": [ "ソトフェール・ファーゾト" ]},
		{ "question": "平面宇宙航行", "answers": [ "ファーゾス" ]},
		{ "question": "平面宇宙航行技術", "answers": [ "ファズ・ファーゾト" ]},
		{ "question": "平面宇宙航行機能", "answers": [ "メーンラジュ" ]},
		{ "question": "平面宇宙航行理論", "answers": [ "クロフェール・ファーゾト" ]},
		{ "question": "幻想園の馬", "answers": [ "ワーフ・ギュームヒュン" ]},
		{ "question": "幻炎", "answers": [ "レニーヴ" ]},
		{ "question": "幻炎作戦", "answers": [ "クファゼート・レニブ" ]},
		{ "question": "幻炎第一七艦隊", "answers": [ "ビュール・キュダナ・レニブ" ]},
		{ "question": "幻炎第一艦隊", "answers": [ "ビュール・カースナ・レニブ" ]},
		{ "question": "幻炎第三艦隊", "answers": [ "ビュール・ビーナ・レニブ" ]},
		{ "question": "幻炎第二艦隊", "answers": [ "ビュール・マータ・レニブ" ]},
		{ "question": "幻炎第五艦隊", "answers": [ "ビュール・リューナ・レニブ" ]},
		{ "question": "幻炎第四艦隊", "answers": [ "ビュール・ゴーナ・レニブ" ]},
		{ "question": "幻炎艦隊", "answers": [ "ビュール・レニブ" ]},
		{ "question": "幻炎艦隊司令部", "answers": [ "グラーガーフ・ビューラル・レニブ" ]},
		{ "question": "幻炎艦隊司令長官", "answers": [ "グラハレル・ビューラル・レネブ" ]},
		{ "question": "幼子", "answers": [ "アソーグ" ]},
		{ "question": "広間", "answers": [ "ワベス" ]},
		{ "question": "座席帯", "answers": [ "アピューフ" ]},
		{ "question": "建国帝", "answers": [ "スクルレトリア" ]},
		{ "question": "建艦厰", "answers": [ "ロール" ]},
		{ "question": "弔いの晩餐", "answers": [ "ギューク・ロボロト" ]},
		{ "question": "強襲輸送艦", "answers": [ "ルソーミア" ]},
		{ "question": "往還機", "answers": [ "フラーシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "往還艇", "answers": [ "フラーシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "後継者", "answers": [ "ゴルキア" ]},
		{ "question": "後衛翔士", "answers": [ "リニェール" ]},
		{ "question": "従士", "answers": [ "サーシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "従士長", "answers": [ "ウェサーシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "忘れじの広間", "answers": [ "グレーシュ・フローネタラ" ]},
		{ "question": "怒り", "answers": [ "セーロス" ]},
		{ "question": "思考結晶", "answers": [ "ダテューキル" ]},
		{ "question": "思考結晶網", "answers": [ "エーフ" ]},
		{ "question": "息子", "answers": [ "フルーク" ]},
		{ "question": "情報局", "answers": [ "スポーデ・リラグ" ]},
		{ "question": "情報局長官", "answers": [ "セーフ・スポーデル・リラグ" ]},
		{ "question": "情報連結", "answers": [ "ロンジョス・リラグ" ]},
		{ "question": "惑乱の淑女", "answers": [ "ロージュ・ラビュルナ" ]},
		{ "question": "惑星改造技師組合", "answers": [ "ガリュール・ファゼール・ディウィム" ]},
		{ "question": "想い出", "answers": [ "ワベード" ]},
		{ "question": "想人", "answers": [ "ヨーフ" ]},
		{ "question": "愚か者", "answers": [ "オーニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "愛しき娘", "answers": [ "ファル・フリューム" ]},
		{ "question": "愛の娘", "answers": [ "フリューム・ネグ" ]},
		{ "question": "愛の息子", "answers": [ "フルーク・ネグ" ]},
		{ "question": "愛の都", "answers": [ "ビロート・ネグ" ]},
		{ "question": "愛娘", "answers": [ "フリューム" ]},
		{ "question": "慣習", "answers": [ "ダルファース" ]},
		{ "question": "成熟", "answers": [ "フェーロス" ]},
		{ "question": "成長", "answers": [ "ザーロス" ]},
		{ "question": "戦い", "answers": [ "スラーショス" ]},
		{ "question": "戦列艦", "answers": [ "アレーク" ]},
		{ "question": "戦士たち", "answers": [ "スラーケラク" ]},
		{ "question": "戦闘指揮卓", "answers": [ "ラトーニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "戦闘配食", "answers": [ "ワニール" ]},
		{ "question": "戦闘開始", "answers": [ "サポルガ" ]},
		{ "question": "戦隊", "answers": [ "ソーヴ" ]},
		{ "question": "戦隊司令部", "answers": [ "グラーガーフ・ソブ" ]},
		{ "question": "所領", "answers": [ "スコール" ]},
		{ "question": "打撃分艦隊", "answers": [ "ヤドビュール・ヴォートゥト" ]},
		{ "question": "打撃戦隊", "answers": [ "ソーヴ・ヴォートゥト" ]},
		{ "question": "技術元帥", "answers": [ "スペーヌ・ファゼール" ]},
		{ "question": "技術者", "answers": [ "ファズィア" ]},
		{ "question": "投降信号", "answers": [ "アーガ・レーガコト" ]},
		{ "question": "折敷", "answers": [ "ドレース" ]},
		{ "question": "抜錨", "answers": [ "ダイセーレ" ]},
		{ "question": "指揮官徽章", "answers": [ "プトラヘデソーフ" ]},
		{ "question": "指揮杖", "answers": [ "グリュー" ]},
		{ "question": "挑戦信号", "answers": [ "アーガ・イゾーフォト" ]},
		{ "question": "捜査", "answers": [ "ナテームコス" ]},
		{ "question": "掌兵科", "answers": [ "ボンデーブ" ]},
		{ "question": "探査参謀", "answers": [ "カーサリア・ラグロト" ]},
		{ "question": "探査担当通信士", "answers": [ "ドロキア・ロイロサセル" ]},
		{ "question": "探査艦隊", "answers": [ "ビュール・ラグレール" ]},
		{ "question": "接続纓", "answers": [ "キセーグ" ]},
		{ "question": "推進剤", "answers": [ "ビーズ" ]},
		{ "question": "推進剤槽", "answers": [ "ビセーク" ]},
		{ "question": "推進銃", "answers": [ "ワーリア" ]},
		{ "question": "提子", "answers": [ "ロズギア" ]},
		{ "question": "提督", "answers": [ "フローデ" ]},
		{ "question": "操作釦", "answers": [ "ポーシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "操泡担当航法士", "answers": [ "リルビガ・フラクトロショサセル" ]},
		{ "question": "操舵士", "answers": [ "セーディア" ]},
		{ "question": "操舵室", "answers": [ "シル・セデール" ]},
		{ "question": "放蕩娘", "answers": [ "ドルフリューム" ]},
		{ "question": "故郷", "answers": [ "ムロート" ]},
		{ "question": "救命莢", "answers": [ "ウィコー" ]},
		{ "question": "教官", "answers": [ "ベセーガ" ]},
		{ "question": "散乱面", "answers": [ "シュノベズィア" ]},
		{ "question": "新たな戦場へ", "answers": [ "ユクラーベ・ディーナ" ]},
		{ "question": "旅立つ者たち", "answers": [ "レプラテラシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "旗", "answers": [ "グラー" ]},
		{ "question": "旗艦", "answers": [ "グラーガ" ]},
		{ "question": "昇降台", "answers": [ "フェレトコーク" ]},
		{ "question": "昇降筒", "answers": [ "ドブロリア" ]},
		{ "question": "星たち", "answers": [ "グリューラシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "星たちの眷族", "answers": [ "カルサール・グリューラク" ]},
		{ "question": "星界軍", "answers": [ "ラブール" ]},
		{ "question": "星界軍元帥げんすい]", "answers": [ "スペーヌ・ラブーラル" ]},
		{ "question": "星界軍翔士", "answers": [ "ラブール・ロダイル" ]},
		{ "question": "星界軍軍士", "answers": [ "ボスナル・ラブーラル" ]},
		{ "question": "星系内航行船", "answers": [ "ポーニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "星間船", "answers": [ "メーニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "星霧", "answers": [ "ヒール" ]},
		{ "question": "時空分離", "answers": [ "ゴール・リュトコス" ]},
		{ "question": "時空泡", "answers": [ "フラサス" ]},
		{ "question": "時空泡発生機関", "answers": [ "フラサティア" ]},
		{ "question": "時空粒子", "answers": [ "スプーフラサス" ]},
		{ "question": "時空融合", "answers": [ "ゴール・プタロス" ]},
		{ "question": "暗号鍵", "answers": [ "セージュ・キームナ" ]},
		{ "question": "書記", "answers": [ "ウィグ" ]},
		{ "question": "有翼竜", "answers": [ "ロース" ]},
		{ "question": "未踏領域", "answers": [ "ソール・ケーラザ" ]},
		{ "question": "本部戦隊", "answers": [ "ソーヴ・グラール" ]},
		{ "question": "林檎酒", "answers": [ "リンメー" ]},
		{ "question": "柑橘果汁", "answers": [ "テュール・ラシュバン" ]},
		{ "question": "核融合弾", "answers": [ "スピュート" ]},
		{ "question": "根源貴族", "answers": [ "クロフェーク" ]},
		{ "question": "桃果汁", "answers": [ "ティル・ノム" ]},
		{ "question": "梯索", "answers": [ "カリュグ" ]},
		{ "question": "検問ラ", "answers": [ "イショス" ]},
		{ "question": "椿の国", "answers": [ "スペシューニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "標準重力", "answers": [ "デモン" ]},
		{ "question": "機動反物質燃料製造工場", "answers": [ "ヨーズ・ホーカ" ]},
		{ "question": "機動時空爆雷", "answers": [ "サテュス・ゴール・ホーカ" ]},
		{ "question": "機動酒保街", "answers": [ "ラクネーヴ・ホーカ" ]},
		{ "question": "機械教師", "answers": [ "オノワレイレ" ]},
		{ "question": "機械清掃員", "answers": [ "クネク・コウィキア" ]},
		{ "question": "機能水晶", "answers": [ "コス・キセーガル" ]},
		{ "question": "機関", "answers": [ "セー" ]},
		{ "question": "機関参謀", "answers": [ "カーサリア・セール" ]},
		{ "question": "機雷", "answers": [ "ホクサス" ]},
		{ "question": "機雷戦", "answers": [ "ホクサティオクス" ]},
		{ "question": "機雷担当砲術士", "answers": [ "トラーキア・ホクササセル" ]},
		{ "question": "檸檬", "answers": [ "ロープ" ]},
		{ "question": "次席翔士", "answers": [ "ロヤルム・ロダイル" ]},
		{ "question": "歎く雉", "answers": [ "クテーシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "殺す", "answers": [ "アゲーム" ]},
		{ "question": "殿下", "answers": [ "フィア" ]},
		{ "question": "母の息子", "answers": [ "フルーク・サーラン" ]},
		{ "question": "氏姓", "answers": [ "フィーズ" ]},
		{ "question": "気密膠剤", "answers": [ "ディーブ" ]},
		{ "question": "気閘室", "answers": [ "ヤドベール" ]},
		{ "question": "気閘室艚口", "answers": [ "ロー・ヤドベル" ]},
		{ "question": "水素運搬船", "answers": [ "カソービア・ベンデル" ]},
		{ "question": "水耕農園", "answers": [ "グレーク" ]},
		{ "question": "決戦前夜", "answers": [ "ゴイライシャカル" ]},
		{ "question": "治療艦", "answers": [ "ジャースィア" ]},
		{ "question": "法衣", "answers": [ "フェクセイ" ]},
		{ "question": "泡間通信", "answers": [ "ドロシュ・フラクテーダル" ]},
		{ "question": "浮揚車", "answers": [ "ウースィア" ]},
		{ "question": "浮揚車発見", "answers": [ "ビリューコス・ウーセル" ]},
		{ "question": "浴室", "answers": [ "ゴーヴ" ]},
		{ "question": "浴布", "answers": [ "ドゥヒュー" ]},
		{ "question": "浴裙", "answers": [ "グーサス" ]},
		{ "question": "海亀の羹", "answers": [ "オートン・フィフェマル" ]},
		{ "question": "液体石鹸", "answers": [ "サテュール" ]},
		{ "question": "淑女", "answers": [ "ロージュ" ]},
		{ "question": "混沌の都", "answers": [ "ビロート・クネーグナ" ]},
		{ "question": "湯殿", "answers": [ "ゴーヴ" ]},
		{ "question": "溶岩松もどき", "answers": [ "ロドールムゼーシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "激情の俘囚", "answers": [ "ロリューク・イサーロト" ]},
		{ "question": "灌水浴", "answers": [ "グーザス" ]},
		{ "question": "灌水浴室", "answers": [ "シル・グーザサル" ]},
		{ "question": "火山", "answers": [ "キーガーフ" ]},
		{ "question": "炭素結晶繊維", "answers": [ "リュルドワ" ]},
		{ "question": "炭素結晶繊維紡錘", "answers": [ "ヨムセー・リュルドワル" ]},
		{ "question": "無重力庭園", "answers": [ "ソムローニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "照明", "answers": [ "アセルタフ" ]},
		{ "question": "燃料", "answers": [ "ベーシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "燃料槽", "answers": [ "ベケーク" ]},
		{ "question": "燃料槽小惑星", "answers": [ "ソブ・ベケーカル" ]},
		{ "question": "燻腿", "answers": [ "リョポス" ]},
		{ "question": "爵位", "answers": [ "スネー" ]},
		{ "question": "父の娘", "answers": [ "フリューム・ローラン" ]},
		{ "question": "父王殿下", "answers": [ "フィア・ローラン" ]},
		{ "question": "片翼頭環", "answers": [ "アルファ・クラブラル" ]},
		{ "question": "物質燃料・推進剤採取基地", "answers": [ "テューフ" ]},
		{ "question": "独立戦隊", "answers": [ "ソーヴ・ゴラザサ" ]},
		{ "question": "猊下", "answers": [ "ニソス","ニソース" ]},
		{ "question": "猫目石", "answers": [ "デセーム" ]},
		{ "question": "玉座", "answers": [ "スケムソール" ]},
		{ "question": "玉杯", "answers": [ "ラムテューシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "王", "answers": [ "ラルス" ]},
		{ "question": "王位", "answers": [ "ラルトラジュ" ]},
		{ "question": "王国", "answers": [ "フェーク" ]},
		{ "question": "王女", "answers": [ "ラルトネー" ]},
		{ "question": "王女殿下", "answers": [ "フィア・ラルトネル" ]},
		{ "question": "王宮", "answers": [ "ラルベイ" ]},
		{ "question": "王家", "answers": [ "ラルティエ" ]},
		{ "question": "王殿下", "answers": [ "フィア・ラルト" ]},
		{ "question": "珈琲", "answers": [ "スルグー" ]},
		{ "question": "珠玉", "answers": [ "ラーフ" ]},
		{ "question": "琥珀", "answers": [ "フティエーニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "男爵", "answers": [ "リューフ" ]},
		{ "question": "男爵の家臣", "answers": [ "ゴスク・リュム" ]},
		{ "question": "男爵家", "answers": [ "リュムジェ" ]},
		{ "question": "男爵閣下", "answers": [ "ローニュ・リュム" ]},
		{ "question": "男爵領", "answers": [ "リュームスコル" ]},
		{ "question": "男爵館", "answers": [ "リューメクス" ]},
		{ "question": "番号", "answers": [ "フタリア" ]},
		{ "question": "異状なし", "answers": [ "ゴスノー" ]},
		{ "question": "異郷への帰還", "answers": [ "サイロス・ロスロータジュ" ]},
		{ "question": "百合の国", "answers": [ "ギュリューニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "百翔長", "answers": [ "ボモワス" ]},
		{ "question": "皇太女", "answers": [ "キルーギア" ]},
		{ "question": "皇太子", "answers": [ "キルーギア" ]},
		{ "question": "皇女", "answers": [ "ルエネー" ]},
		{ "question": "皇女殿下", "answers": [ "フィア・ルエネル" ]},
		{ "question": "皇孫女", "answers": [ "ルエボグネー" ]},
		{ "question": "皇孫女殿下", "answers": [ "フィア・ルエボグネル" ]},
		{ "question": "皇帝", "answers": [ "スピュネージュ" ]},
		{ "question": "皇帝杖", "answers": [ "ルエグリュー" ]},
		{ "question": "皇帝陛下", "answers": [ "スピュネージュ・エルミタ" ]},
		{ "question": "皇族", "answers": [ "ファサンゼール" ]},
		{ "question": "監督", "answers": [ "ビュヌケール" ]},
		{ "question": "直轄艦", "answers": [ "グラーバウリア" ]},
		{ "question": "真の翔士", "answers": [ "ロダイル・ノークタ" ]},
		{ "question": "真珠", "answers": [ "ラーフ" ]},
		{ "question": "真空", "answers": [ "ダーズ" ]},
		{ "question": "真空世界", "answers": [ "ダーズ" ]},
		{ "question": "真空空間", "answers": [ "ダーズ" ]},
		{ "question": "短艇", "answers": [ "カリーク" ]},
		{ "question": "短針銃", "answers": [ "ケーリア" ]},
		{ "question": "砂芝", "answers": [ "ロンレーヴ" ]},
		{ "question": "砲術参謀", "answers": [ "カーサリア・トラショト" ]},
		{ "question": "砲術士", "answers": [ "トラーキア" ]},
		{ "question": "硝子杯", "answers": [ "スィニューク" ]},
		{ "question": "称号", "answers": [ "トライガ" ]},
		{ "question": "移動壇", "answers": [ "ヤーズリア" ]},
		{ "question": "移動状態", "answers": [ "ノークタフ" ]},
		{ "question": "空挺艦隊", "answers": [ "ビュール・ワケール" ]},
		{ "question": "空識覚", "answers": [ "フロクラジュ" ]},
		{ "question": "空識覚器官", "answers": [ "フローシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "空間庭園", "answers": [ "デーヴ" ]},
		{ "question": "空間放浪時代", "answers": [ "ゴー・ラムゴコト" ]},
		{ "question": "空間機動要塞", "answers": [ "ロニーデ・ホーカ" ]},
		{ "question": "突撃分艦隊", "answers": [ "ヤドビュール・アシャル" ]},
		{ "question": "突撃戦隊", "answers": [ "ソーヴ・アシャル" ]},
		{ "question": "突撃艦", "answers": [ "ゲール" ]},
		{ "question": "突撃艦長", "answers": [ "マノワス・ゲル" ]},
		{ "question": "突撃隊", "answers": [ "スューフ・アシャル" ]},
		{ "question": "突撃隊司令", "answers": [ "サレール・スュム・アシャル" ]},
		{ "question": "竜", "answers": [ "ノーシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "竜の頸の付根", "answers": [ "サース・ノーシャル" ]},
		{ "question": "端末", "answers": [ "ソテュア" ]},
		{ "question": "端末腕環", "answers": [ "クリューノ" ]},
		{ "question": "第一○五八突撃戦隊", "answers": [ "ソーヴ・アシャル・キュトポルリュガナ" ]},
		{ "question": "第一二七船渠", "answers": [ "ルー・キュトマダナ" ]},
		{ "question": "第一八四打撃戦隊", "answers": [ "ソーヴ・ヴォートゥト・キガゴナ" ]},
		{ "question": "第一四艦隊", "answers": [ "ビュール・キュドゴナ" ]},
		{ "question": "第一王女", "answers": [ "ラルトネー・カースナ" ]},
		{ "question": "第一環", "answers": [ "スペーシュ・カースナ" ]},
		{ "question": "第一突撃隊", "answers": [ "スューフ・アシャル・カースナ" ]},
		{ "question": "第一級臨戦態勢", "answers": [ "ヨグドズヴォス・カースナ" ]},
		{ "question": "第一艦隊", "answers": [ "ビュール・カースナ" ]},
		{ "question": "第一艦隊司令長官", "answers": [ "グラハレル・ビューラル・カースナ" ]},
		{ "question": "第七環", "answers": [ "スペーシュ・ダーナ" ]},
		{ "question": "第三艦隊", "answers": [ "ビュール・ビーナ" ]},
		{ "question": "第二環", "answers": [ "スペーシュ・マータ" ]},
		{ "question": "第二級臨戦態勢", "answers": [ "ヨグドズヴォス・マータ" ]},
		{ "question": "第二艦隊", "answers": [ "ビュール・マータ" ]},
		{ "question": "第二配膳室", "answers": [ "シル・スポーロト・マータ" ]},
		{ "question": "第五艦隊", "answers": [ "ビュール・リューナ" ]},
		{ "question": "第八環", "answers": [ "スペーシュ・ガーナ" ]},
		{ "question": "第十一工場", "answers": [ "ヨーズ・ロキュトナ" ]},
		{ "question": "第十一環", "answers": [ "スペーシュ・ロキュトナ" ]},
		{ "question": "第十二環", "answers": [ "スペーシュ・ロマータ" ]},
		{ "question": "第四突撃隊", "answers": [ "スューフ・アシャル・ゴーナ" ]},
		{ "question": "第四艦隊", "answers": [ "ビュール・ゴーナ" ]},
		{ "question": "管制", "answers": [ "ブリューセ" ]},
		{ "question": "管制官", "answers": [ "ブルーセガ" ]},
		{ "question": "管制室", "answers": [ "シル・ブリューセガル" ]},
		{ "question": "管制室主任家士", "answers": [ "アルム・ブリューセガ" ]},
		{ "question": "管制機能", "answers": [ "ブリューセラジュ" ]},
		{ "question": "箸", "answers": [ "グレー" ]},
		{ "question": "紅玉", "answers": [ "ドゥー" ]},
		{ "question": "紅茶", "answers": [ "ソイ・アーサ" ]},
		{ "question": "紋章", "answers": [ "アージュ" ]},
		{ "question": "紋章旗", "answers": [ "ガール・グラー" ]},
		{ "question": "紋章院", "answers": [ "ガール・スカス" ]},
		{ "question": "紡錘", "answers": [ "ヨムセー" ]},
		{ "question": "紫水晶", "answers": [ "ブレスキル" ]},
		{ "question": "組合", "answers": [ "ガリュール" ]},
		{ "question": "絆のかたち", "answers": [ "クレース・スィトン" ]},
		{ "question": "経理従士", "answers": [ "サーシュ・スケル" ]},
		{ "question": "結晶網", "answers": [ "エーフ" ]},
		{ "question": "結晶陶質", "answers": [ "リュアボン" ]},
		{ "question": "結線", "answers": [ "キューム" ]},
		{ "question": "給仕", "answers": [ "バーティア" ]},
		{ "question": "統帥府", "answers": [ "ワロディアシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "網", "answers": [ "エーフ" ]},
		{ "question": "緊急事態", "answers": [ "レスリアムロス" ]},
		{ "question": "緑茶", "answers": [ "ソイ・アーラ" ]},
		{ "question": "練習艦", "answers": [ "クレーヤガ" ]},
		{ "question": "練習艦隊", "answers": [ "ビュール・クレーヤル" ]},
		{ "question": "義務", "answers": [ "スレムコス" ]},
		{ "question": "翔士", "answers": [ "ロダイル" ]},
		{ "question": "翔士修技生", "answers": [ "ベネー・ロダイル" ]},
		{ "question": "翔士修技館", "answers": [ "ケンルー・ロイダル" ]},
		{ "question": "翔士適性審査", "answers": [ "ラデゥラジュ・ブークラグ" ]},
		{ "question": "翡翠の玉座", "answers": [ "スケムソール・レン" ]},
		{ "question": "育児休暇", "answers": [ "カグゾフォス" ]},
		{ "question": "育児園", "answers": [ "ソムローニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "腰帯", "answers": [ "ウェーヴ" ]},
		{ "question": "膠剤", "answers": [ "ディーブ" ]},
		{ "question": "臣民", "answers": [ "ビサール" ]},
		{ "question": "自動機械", "answers": [ "オヌホーキア" ]},
		{ "question": "自走鞄", "answers": [ "ダグボーシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "舞踏の女神", "answers": [ "フトゥーネ" ]},
		{ "question": "航法参謀", "answers": [ "カーサリア・リルビコト" ]},
		{ "question": "航法士", "answers": [ "リルビガ" ]},
		{ "question": "航法野", "answers": [ "リルビドー" ]},
		{ "question": "航路", "answers": [ "ビール" ]},
		{ "question": "舷門歓迎式", "answers": [ "パトムサイホス" ]},
		{ "question": "船", "answers": [ "メーニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "船乗り", "answers": [ "ソーク" ]},
		{ "question": "船艙", "answers": [ "ホール" ]},
		{ "question": "艇指揮", "answers": [ "ポノワス" ]},
		{ "question": "艇長", "answers": [ "ポノワス" ]},
		{ "question": "艇長徽章", "answers": [ "ブセスパス" ]},
		{ "question": "艚口", "answers": [ "ロー" ]},
		{ "question": "艦政本部長官", "answers": [ "セーフ・ヴォボト・メニョト" ]},
		{ "question": "艦橋", "answers": [ "ガホール" ]},
		{ "question": "艦章旗", "answers": [ "グラー・モンガール" ]},
		{ "question": "艦船", "answers": [ "メーニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "艦長", "answers": [ "サレール","マノワス" ]},
		{ "question": "艦長称号", "answers": [ "サレラジュ" ]},
		{ "question": "艦隊", "answers": [ "ビュール" ]},
		{ "question": "艦隊副官", "answers": [ "ルーキア・ビューラル" ]},
		{ "question": "艦隊司令長官", "answers": [ "グラハレル・ビューラル" ]},
		{ "question": "艦隊旗", "answers": [ "グラー・ビューラル" ]},
		{ "question": "艦隊旗艦", "answers": [ "グラーガ・ビューラル" ]},
		{ "question": "花押", "answers": [ "グナファス" ]},
		{ "question": "薔薇の国", "answers": [ "パリューニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "薬剤科", "answers": [ "クリューリア" ]},
		{ "question": "薬剤科翔士", "answers": [ "ロダイル・クリューレール" ]},
		{ "question": "衛生従士", "answers": [ "サーシュ・リアレル" ]},
		{ "question": "衣裳係", "answers": [ "ダウシャセール" ]},
		{ "question": "衣裳筐", "answers": [ "ラワーフ" ]},
		{ "question": "装帯", "answers": [ "クタレーヴ" ]},
		{ "question": "補給分艦隊", "answers": [ "ヤドビュール・ディクポーレール" ]},
		{ "question": "補給参謀", "answers": [ "カーサリア・ソベール" ]},
		{ "question": "補給戦隊", "answers": [ "ソーヴ・ディクポーレール" ]},
		{ "question": "補給艦", "answers": [ "ディーホスフ" ]},
		{ "question": "訓練生", "answers": [ "ケーニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "訓育教官", "answers": [ "ベセーガ" ]},
		{ "question": "記憶巣", "answers": [ "ボワゼプク" ]},
		{ "question": "記憶片", "answers": [ "ジェーシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "誕生室", "answers": [ "ピュア" ]},
		{ "question": "諸上皇の間", "answers": [ "ワベス・ファニガラク" ]},
		{ "question": "諸侯", "answers": [ "ヴォーダ" ]},
		{ "question": "諸侯家", "answers": [ "ヴォーダジェ" ]},
		{ "question": "諸規則", "answers": [ "リウェール" ]},
		{ "question": "謁見の広間", "answers": [ "ワベス・ベゾーロト" ]},
		{ "question": "識別電波紋", "answers": [ "デファス" ]},
		{ "question": "警衛従士", "answers": [ "サーシュ・レートフェク" ]},
		{ "question": "警鐘", "answers": [ "ドゥニート" ]},
		{ "question": "護衛戦隊", "answers": [ "ソーヴ・メスゲール" ]},
		{ "question": "護衛艦", "answers": [ "レート" ]},
		{ "question": "護衛隊", "answers": [ "スューフ・メスゲール" ]},
		{ "question": "貨客船", "answers": [ "レビサーズ" ]},
		{ "question": "貴族", "answers": [ "スィーフ" ]},
		{ "question": "貴族社会", "answers": [ "スィームフェ" ]},
		{ "question": "貿易港", "answers": [ "ビドート・アーサ" ]},
		{ "question": "質量波", "answers": [ "セースラズ" ]},
		{ "question": "軌道城館", "answers": [ "ガリーシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "軌道塔", "answers": [ "アルネージュ" ]},
		{ "question": "軌道宮殿", "answers": [ "ベイ" ]},
		{ "question": "軍事基地", "answers": [ "ロニード" ]},
		{ "question": "軍令本部", "answers": [ "リュアゾーニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "軍令本部情報局", "answers": [ "リュアゾーニュ・スポーデ・リラグ" ]},
		{ "question": "軍令長官", "answers": [ "ワロズ・リュアゾン" ]},
		{ "question": "軍匠列翼翔士", "answers": [ "フェクトダイ・スケム" ]},
		{ "question": "軍匠十翔長", "answers": [ "ローワス・スケム" ]},
		{ "question": "軍匠科", "answers": [ "スケーフ" ]},
		{ "question": "軍匠科翔士", "answers": [ "ロダイル・スケム" ]},
		{ "question": "軍医", "answers": [ "ガイリート" ]},
		{ "question": "軍医科", "answers": [ "ガイリート" ]},
		{ "question": "軍士", "answers": [ "ボスナル" ]},
		{ "question": "軍大学", "answers": [ "ヴォスクラ" ]},
		{ "question": "軍役", "answers": [ "スリュームコス" ]},
		{ "question": "軍楽従士", "answers": [ "サーシュ・アロヴォト" ]},
		{ "question": "軍艦", "answers": [ "ウィクリュール" ]},
		{ "question": "軍衣", "answers": [ "セリーヌ" ]},
		{ "question": "軽輸送艦", "answers": [ "イサーズ・ソーラ" ]},
		{ "question": "軽量艇", "answers": [ "メーニュ・ソーナ" ]},
		{ "question": "輝く者", "answers": [ "セーリア" ]},
		{ "question": "輸送艦", "answers": [ "イサーズ" ]},
		{ "question": "追撃戦", "answers": [ "ウェフソス" ]},
		{ "question": "逃走", "answers": [ "ディヘロス" ]},
		{ "question": "透明面頬", "answers": [ "オベート" ]},
		{ "question": "通信", "answers": [ "ドロシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "通信参謀", "answers": [ "カーサリア・ドロショト" ]},
		{ "question": "通信基地", "answers": [ "ロニード・ドロク" ]},
		{ "question": "通信士", "answers": [ "ドロキア" ]},
		{ "question": "通信艦隊", "answers": [ "ビュール・ドロケール","ビュール・ドロク" ]},
		{ "question": "通常宇宙", "answers": [ "ダーズ" ]},
		{ "question": "通常空間戦", "answers": [ "ダディオクス" ]},
		{ "question": "通話器", "answers": [ "ルオーデ" ]},
		{ "question": "造兵修技館", "answers": [ "ケンルー・ファゼール・ロウボン" ]},
		{ "question": "造兵科", "answers": [ "ファズィア・ロウボン" ]},
		{ "question": "造機科", "answers": [ "ファズィア・セール" ]},
		{ "question": "造船修技館", "answers": [ "ケンルー・ファゼール・ハル" ]},
		{ "question": "造船技師", "answers": [ "ファズィア・ハル" ]},
		{ "question": "造船科", "answers": [ "ファズィア・ハル" ]},
		{ "question": "造船翔士", "answers": [ "ロダイル・ファゼール・ハル" ]},
		{ "question": "連絡船", "answers": [ "パウリア" ]},
		{ "question": "連絡艇", "answers": [ "ペリア" ]},
		{ "question": "連絡艦", "answers": [ "ロンギア" ]},
		{ "question": "運搬船", "answers": [ "カソービア" ]},
		{ "question": "遺伝子提供者", "answers": [ "ラルリーヌ" ]},
		{ "question": "遺伝子検査", "answers": [ "ヤナルムコス" ]},
		{ "question": "遺伝要素", "answers": [ "デルラーシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "邦国", "answers": [ "アイス" ]},
		{ "question": "都", "answers": [ "ビロート" ]},
		{ "question": "酒精", "answers": [ "スキアデ" ]},
		{ "question": "重力制御", "answers": [ "ワムロス" ]},
		{ "question": "重力制御機関", "answers": [ "ワムリア" ]},
		{ "question": "金剛石", "answers": [ "ラテクリル" ]},
		{ "question": "金色烏", "answers": [ "ガサルス" ]},
		{ "question": "銀の枝と蝸牛", "answers": [ "ヤーズ・シュレンナ・ル・クラスビュール" ]},
		{ "question": "鋼の心", "answers": [ "ソク・ジェンナ" ]},
		{ "question": "鍵", "answers": [ "セージュ" ]},
		{ "question": "鍵盤", "answers": [ "セゲース" ]},
		{ "question": "鍵語", "answers": [ "セジョス" ]},
		{ "question": "鎮守府", "answers": [ "シュテューム" ]},
		{ "question": "鎮守府副司令長官", "answers": [ "ロイグラハレル・シュテューマル" ]},
		{ "question": "鎮守府副長官", "answers": [ "ロイグラハレル・シュテューマル" ]},
		{ "question": "鎮守府司令長官", "answers": [ "グラハレル・シュテューマル" ]},
		{ "question": "鎮守府本部", "answers": [ "バンゾール・シュテューマル" ]},
		{ "question": "長衣", "answers": [ "ダウシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "門", "answers": [ "ソード" ]},
		{ "question": "閉じた門", "answers": [ "ソード・レーザ" ]},
		{ "question": "開いた門", "answers": [ "ソード・グラーカ" ]},
		{ "question": "閘門", "answers": [ "ソヒュース" ]},
		{ "question": "閣下", "answers": [ "ローニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "防御機雷戦", "answers": [ "ホクサティオクス・メジョト" ]},
		{ "question": "防御磁場", "answers": [ "スネセーブ" ]},
		{ "question": "防御磁場発生機関", "answers": [ "スネセーブガ" ]},
		{ "question": "防衛戦", "answers": [ "レクポロス" ]},
		{ "question": "防衛艦隊", "answers": [ "レクポリア" ]},
		{ "question": "防衛艦隊司令部", "answers": [ "ガラーガーフ・レクポレール" ]},
		{ "question": "降伏の儀式", "answers": [ "ドニー・レヒアコト" ]},
		{ "question": "陛下", "answers": [ "エルミタ","エルミトン" ]},
		{ "question": "陥ちざるもの", "answers": [ "ダワトサリア" ]},
		{ "question": "隊", "answers": [ "スューフ" ]},
		{ "question": "階級", "answers": [ "レーニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "隠し", "answers": [ "モスク" ]},
		{ "question": "集合信号", "answers": [ "アーガ・アスパロト" ]},
		{ "question": "集合邸宅", "answers": [ "バーシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "離着甲板", "answers": [ "ゴリアーヴ" ]},
		{ "question": "電波紋", "answers": [ "デファス" ]},
		{ "question": "電波紋鍵", "answers": [ "セージュ・デファト" ]},
		{ "question": "電波虫", "answers": [ "デムブース" ]},
		{ "question": "電波通信", "answers": [ "ドロシュ・デム" ]},
		{ "question": "電磁投射砲", "answers": [ "イルギューフ" ]},
		{ "question": "青年", "answers": [ "ワンシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "領主", "answers": [ "ファピュート" ]},
		{ "question": "領主代行", "answers": [ "クファリア" ]},
		{ "question": "領主副代行", "answers": [ "ロイクファリア" ]},
		{ "question": "領地", "answers": [ "リビューヌ" ]},
		{ "question": "領域", "answers": [ "ソール" ]},
		{ "question": "領民", "answers": [ "ソス" ]},
		{ "question": "領民代表", "answers": [ "セーフ・ソス" ]},
		{ "question": "領民政府", "answers": [ "セメイ・ソス" ]},
		{ "question": "頭環", "answers": [ "アルファ" ]},
		{ "question": "飛燕草", "answers": [ "リゼール" ]},
		{ "question": "飛燕草の広間", "answers": [ "ワベス・リゼル" ]},
		{ "question": "飛翔科", "answers": [ "ガーリア","ガレール" ]},
		{ "question": "飛翔科翔士", "answers": [ "ロダイル・ガレール" ]},
		{ "question": "飾帯", "answers": [ "クタレーヴ" ]},
		{ "question": "餐堂", "answers": [ "ビスィアフ" ]},
		{ "question": "馬上試合", "answers": [ "リエ・ドレール" ]},
		{ "question": "駆動炎", "answers": [ "アソート" ]},
		{ "question": "高坏", "answers": [ "スカリューシュ" ]},
		{ "question": "高山", "answers": [ "ガーフ・ラーカ" ]},
		{ "question": "高等法院", "answers": [ "スカス・ラザソト" ]},
		{ "question": "鱒の麭包み", "answers": [ "デルスルーフ・ボス" ]},
		{ "question": "麗しき者", "answers": [ "ノーウォン" ]},
		{ "question": "麗しき頑固者", "answers": [ "クラソーノン・ノーワ" ]},
		{ "question": "麻酔銃", "answers": [ "リブアスィア" ]}
	]
}
